His Majesty's edict is here!
This is His Majesty's verbal orders.
The cases of Jiang Li breaking a prisoner
out of jail and Xue Huaiyuan's corruption
will be tried together
at the Court of Judicial Review.
Duke Su is the imperial commissioner
who will supervise the investigation
on His Majesty's behalf.
The case will be presented
before His Majesty
ten days later to judge the case.
- Long live His Majesty!
Old Madam, don't worry.
Have some pear soup.
Dear,
did it go well with His Majesty?
What did His Majesty say?
His Majesty wouldn't meet me at all.
Well…
What does His Majesty mean?
His Majesty is making me avoid suspicions.
Don't worry too much, dear.
Tomorrow, I'll enter the palace
to ask Consort Li about it.
I'm sorry to let you
run around because of this.
What are you saying?
Although I'm just a homemaker,
I know what's at stake.
This doesn't only concern Li'er's survival
but also the Jiang family's reputation.
I won't just stand by and do nothing.
It's great for you to think that.
It's just pitiful that Li'er is locked up
at the Court of Judicial Review.
And it's also bad
for the Jiang family's reputation.
I've heard some rumors
even from here.
They said the Jiang family's daughter
is no longer pure
after being locked up.
Even the Jiang family's name
can't be cleared.
Mother.
It's not that I don't want to save her,
but she is really…
Well…
We are not completely helpless
in this case.
What do you mean?
Previously, there was a rule
at the capital's government office.
If a woman commits a crime,
as long as it's not killing
her husband or children,
she can be
supervised back home
by her husband or family members
and await for her summon.
The Court of Judicial Review
might be great,
but it's still
the capital's government office.
Since Li'er is not married,
the Jiang family will supervise her.
Good.
I'll write to the minister
of the Court of Judicial Review tomorrow.
There's no need for you to write.
You've worked hard and long
to deal with the Dingzhou issue.
It's better
for the Jiang family's women
to handle this.
You mean…
Don't worry.
I will surely bring Li'er back.
COURT OF JUDICIAL REVIEW
You've been reminding me
to stay calm over and over again,
but I still failed to do so.
I expected that,
but I didn't guess you'd be so pitiful.
Aren't you a particular person?
Don't you find this place dirty?
I'm tired,
so I'll rest here a bit.
I heard you were ordered
to supervise the investigation.
But you haven't asked anything
about the case.
Aren't you afraid
His Majesty will punish you?
You've been asking me questions
since I came in.
Aren't you tired?
Yes.
I'm quite tired.
The Admonishment Drum was beaten
and His Majesty will judge it himself.
You are forcing them
to back you into a corner.
You've tried too hard.
It's not the first time.
There's actually no need to do that.
Duke Su,
is there anyone around you
who died unjustly?
Father, wake up!
Father!
Wake up, Father!
If you were given an opportunity,
would you strike the Admonishment Drum
at the Chang'an Gate for them?
I think you would.
All right.
I'm done investigating.
Is that all?
Yes.
Haven't you said all you need to say?
I'll go ahead.
Get some rest.
You shouldn't have come to this place.
And as the wife of the Chief Secretariat,
it's not right to show yourself here.
Don't restrict me with these words.
I've been managing the Jiang household
for more than a decade.
Although I can't see most things
in the government office,
I still hear about many things.
Now that you have my daughter here,
do you think it's unreasonable
for me to ask about her?
If you just want to see the criminal,
I can help you with that.
However, you are here to take her away.
Forgive me for not allowing that.
I just want to ask you
two questions, Duke Zhou.
First.
As a judicial officer,
do you follow the law of Great Yan?
Of course.
Second.
When a woman commits a crime,
as long as she didn't
kill her husband or children,
she can be taken home
to be supervised
by her husband or family members
while waiting to be summoned
before the trial.
Is this one of the laws of Great Yan?
Well…
Yes.
In that case,
why can't I set foot in this place?
I came here today
because I insisted
on picking up my daughter.
I want to see
who dares to stop me.
Guard.
Yes.
Bring Ms. Jiang Li here.
I'll be waiting here then.
- Duke Su.
What's the matter?
The minister asked us
to hand over the criminal
for supervision by her family.
We are here to take her out.
Duke Zhou, she's here.
Mrs. Jiang.
Based on Great Yan's law,
she'll be handed over
to the Jiang family for supervision.
If she goes missing or is hidden,
you will be punished according to the law.
Thank you, Duke Zhou.
Don't move around.
Just leave with me.
Mother, why are you here?
I don't know why you insisted
on overturning that magistrate's case
after returning to Luyang,
but I know
your father has grown
a lot of gray hair
because of what you did.
You've let your father
and the Jiang family down.
As your mother,
I can't ignore your father
and the reputation of the Jiang family.
When you return to the Jiang family,
you can explain
to your father and Old Madam yourself.
You are right, Mother.
Grandmother,
I have returned.
It's good that you're home.
Sit.
Do you know why your father
doesn't want to see you?
I'm sure Father
was worried about me
with what happened in Dingzhou.
I caused such a big trouble.
I'm sure Father is angry at me.
You are not related
to the magistrate from the Xue family.
Why did you get yourself involved
in such a case?
You even brought so many folks
back to the capital
and risked your life
and the future of the Jiang family.
Magistrate Xue's daughter, Xue Fangfei,
was my savior.
When I was in Zhennv Hall,
the Chief mistreated me
and I almost died.
It was Xue Fangfei who saved me.
Something like that happened?
I went to Luyang
not only to visit my relatives
but also to meet my savior.
However, she passed away at a young age.
Her father was in trouble
and I couldn't just stand by.
Li'er,
I won't stop you
if you want to repay a debt of kindness,
but did you have to do that this way?
I know.
I'm part of the Jiang family.
Every move I make
will affect the Jiang family,
so it wasn't my intention
to act recklessly.
I only wanted to go to Huaixiang
to meet my savior at first.
After I arrived in Huaixiang,
I accidentally discovered
that the new magistrate
was lawles,
disregarded human lives,
and exploited people.
You didn't see it.
Huaixiang was a prosperous place,
but it fell into a state
where people dared not step out
during the day.
It was very sad.
Grandmother,
you told me about the family rules
Grandfather set.
Protect justice,
maintain righteousness,
and not covet temporary fame.
It's exactly because
I'm part of the Jiang family
that I couldn't ignore
the aggrieved and suffering people.
I'm very happy to see
that you have such integrity.
However, you could have told
your father about it
and let him handle it.
You didn't need to put yourself
in danger again and again.
I had no choice.
The new Huaixiang magistrate
I told you about just now
colluded with the Li family.
What?
In the Soochow brocade incident
of the Ye family in Luyang,
someone purposely placed poison
to frame the Ye family.
I wrote a letter
to inform Father about that.
I also found clues in Luyang.
The Li family is most probably
the mastermind behind this.
Are you going to overturn
the convicted official's case next?
Since ancient times,
there have been countless wronged cases.
Only a few could be overturned.
After breaking
a death row prisoner out of jail,
I heard you'll be executed
if you can't overturn the case.
Grandmother,
I've gotten Xue Huaiyuan's dossier.
The case is a mess
and full of flaws.
Besides, if Magistrate Xue is guilty,
so many people
won't come with me
to petition to His Majesty.
And the new magistrate,
supported by the Li family,
bullied the people
and was nefarious.
People hate him.
I'll tell your father about this.
Thank you, Grandmother.
What?
The magistrate of Huaixiang
really works for the Li family?
Exactly.
Li and Jiang families
never saw eye to eye.
Over the years,
the Li family has been nurturing its power
in and out of the imperial court.
Meanwhile, the Jiang family
is not the same as it used to be.
I'm sure you know this
better than anyone else.
The Li family has made their move.
Are we going to turn a blind eye to it?
No wonder Li Zhongnan
wrote the memorial himself this time
and wants Jiang Li dead.
You've finally understood.
If Xue Huaiyuan's case can be overturned,
it'd be a setback
for the Li family indeed.
However, Li Zhongnan
will also hold a grudge against us.
When he gets an opportunity in the future,
he will take revenge
on the Jiang family like crazy.
Even if you don't do anything,
will the Li family stop hating us?
They started the whole thing
and they even harmed the Ye family.
The Ye family
is our in-laws.
If we don't do anything,
how will people view the Jiang family?
Although Li'er acts
on her passion for righteousness alone
and seems reckless
in hitting the Admonishment Drum,
His Majesty said
he would judge the case himself.
That means His Majesty also noticed
something fishy about Xue Huaiyuan's case.
Doesn't that
give us a chance to counterattack?
Shuran has brought Li'er back now.
We have nothing to be afraid of.
At this point,
we should help Li'er
and give the Li family a blow.
Did you miss her?
What do you mean?
I thought you came back late
because you went
to the Court of Judicial Review
to see Jiang Li,
who looks the same as your late wife.
Stop!
You are so boring.
You can't be teased at all.
Help me see
which outfit suits my complexion more.
Help me take a look.
Which outfit suits my complexion more?
All bright colors suit you.
Don't you prefer plain colors?
That's because I'm lowly.
All right.
I'll choose the red outfit then.
I'll wear it
to meet Ms. Jiang Li.
Why is Your Highness
going to the trial tomorrow?
To rub salt into the wound, of course.
I hope you don't start a fire
and burn yourself.
Shen Yurong,
I've tolerated you for a long time.
Your Highness, please turn around.
I'll help you tidy your sleeves.
I've always wanted to know
that if given another chance,
would you bury Xue Fangfei
or kill me?
I'd rather
die in Your Highness' hands.
TAIJI HALL
Ms. Jiang Li.
Why isn't Jiang Yuanbai here with you?
I think you've gotten used to the prison
in the Court of Judicial Review.
You've become brave now.
You must be Chancellor Li.
Thank you for your concern.
I've already been released
from the prison.
The Chief Secretariat
has always been discreet.
I didn't expect his daughter
to be courageous.
Now that you've become more capable,
it's really surprising.
I'm flattered, Chancellor Li.
It seems like you're confident.
Are you sure they'll reveal
my involvement today,
so you don't feel scared at all?
What are you thinking?
Are you thinking how I know about this?
Let me tell you this,
Ms. Jiang Li.
There's nothing in this world
that I don't know of.
You are too naive
if you plan to play tricks
in front of me.
Even your father dares not do that,
but a young girl like you
is so discontented.
Are you not afraid
that you might die
without a grave to your name in the end?
Are you reminding me to leave a way out
for a surrounded enemy
and not press too hard?
Ms. Jiang Li, you are really brave.
You are so much better
than the two incapable sons of mine.
I just wonder how long
you can keep your bravery up.
After today's ruling by His Majesty
and there's no room for maneuver,
I'm afraid Jiang Yuanbai
will have no choice but to abandon you.
Chancellor Li.
Duke Su, you are early as well.
I was standing far away
and couldn't hear you clearly.
What were you saying
to educate Ms. Jiang Li?
She even mentioned leaving a way out
for a surrounded enemy.
I was rude.
Ms. Jiang Li,
what you said comes from The Art of War.
It's aggressive.
If you meet an old official
like Chancellor Li in the future,
you must speak cautiously.
Understood.
Duke Su, you sure take good care of her.
Not really.
I'm just better
at teaching others than you,
Chancellor Li.
We still don't know
the results of today's trial.
Ms. Jiang Li is confident now.
I hope she can still smile
like she does now when the trial ends.
If you will excuse me.
Duke Su, thank you
for helping me get off the hook again.
That was not a hook
for you.
You can't say that.
At least I can see
that Li Zhongnan came prepared.
In that case,
I have to tell you something in advance.
Relax.
I'm not planning
to hand my pawn over to the opponent yet.
If that's the case,
I must offer my gift
to express my gratitude.
I've been trapped at home recently.
The handkerchief
you asked me to sew is done.
You have great embroidery skills.
My embroidery skills cannot be compared
to the one who sews your handkerchief.
I didn't even dare sew it at first,
fearing I'd ruin the work of the deceased.
You studied my background.
Duke Su, your father, General Xiao,
was a famous general of our nation.
He was a soldier his whole life.
The whole nation knows that.
He and Madam Yu were deeply in love.
She was also an admirable
and respectable woman.
What about your father?
What about me?
Chancellor Jiang.
Chancellor Jiang, you think thoroughly
and love the people.
I have something to say to my daughter.
Father.
You've suffered.
I thought you would never forgive me.
You are my daughter after all.
Your grandmother told me your sentiments.
Don't be scared later.
Just say anything on your mind.
I have your back.
Thank you, Father.
His Majesty is here!
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise, everyone.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
The corruption case
of Huaixiang's magistrate, Xue Huaiyuan,
was judged by the local government office
and the dossier was handed
to the Ministry of Justice
for closure.
Now, the people of Huaixiang
doubt the result of the case
and appeal for him
and His Majesty cares
for the people, so he ordered
the Ministry of Justice to hand it back
to the Court of Judicial Review.
The Court of Judicial Review's minister
will handle the case
and retry it together
with the Ministry of Justice.
The trial today
will be supervised by His Majesty himself.
Minister Zhou.
- You may begin.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Summon Ms. Jiang Li.
Summon Ms. Jiang Li!
I, Jiang Li, greet Your Majesty.
Rise and speak.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Ms. Jiang Li,
did you bring the people of Huaixiang
into the capital
for the sake
of the corruption case of Xue Huaiyuan,
the magistrate of Huaixiang?
Minister Zhou,
half a year ago,
Huaixiang's magistrate, Xue Huaiyuan,
was accused of embezzlement
by a local government office officer,
Feng Yutang.
He was judged to be executed
by the Ministry of Justice
and awaited execution in prison.
I went to Huaixiang to visit a friend
and accidentally discovered
something fishy in this case.
According to my understanding,
all of you
barged into Huaixiang's government office
on the day of Xue Huaiyuan's execution
and took the prisoner away forcefully.
Do you admit that?
I do.
Then do you know
that breaking a prisoner out of jail from
a government office is a serious crime?
I do.
It was a last resort.
But if we hadn't done that,
Xue Huaiyuan's grievance
and the suffering of Huaixiang's people
would never be known.
I will take responsibility
for the crime I committed.
But I hope Your Majesty and everyone here
can redress the injustice
for Magistrate Xue before convicting me.
Who was in charge
of Xue Huaiyuan's case
at the Ministry of Justice?
I was.
I remember
that the dossier of this case
was not complicated.
Ten crates of silver were found
in Xue Huaiyuan's residence,
totaling 5,000 taels,
as well as a private ledger.
Along with the testimony of the local
government office officer, Feng Yutang,
we both had evidence and a witness.
There was nothing fishy,
as Ms. Jiang Li mentioned.
Ms. Jiang Li went to Huaixiang personally.
I think she has discovered
something unknown to others.
Since you are trying
to overturn the case for a criminal,
please present new evidence
in front of His Majesty
and let us judge it.
I have no new evidence.
How dare you?
Since you have no new evidence,
how dare you trick people
into coming to the capital
to sound the Admonishment Drum
and force His Majesty to retry the case?
Ms. Jiang Li,
you have no respect
for His Majesty at all.
My daughter is not done talking yet.
What's the rush?
Since I can't present new evidence,
I will change my request.
Your Majesty,
I came all the way
with the people of Huaixiang
to sound the Admonishment Drum,
not to help Xue Huaiyuan get acquitted
but to ask Your Majesty to convict him.
Silence!
Convict him?
What do you mean?
As you all know,
there's concrete evidence
for the embezzlement
of Huaixiang's magistrate, Xue Huaiyuan.
He's a vermin of the imperial court.
Your Majesty prioritizes integrity.
How dare a mere magistrate of Huaixiang
be so daring?
Imprisonment and execution
cannot appease angry people.
I think
he should be punished
with death by a thousand slashes.
Didn't she say
she was going to overturn the case?
Is she admitting defeat
because she has no evidence?
Xue Huaiyuan might have a lowly position,
but he was still an official of Great Yan.
He was an official
in Huaixiang for a decade
and they only discovered
his corruption last year
and the evidence was a mere 5,000 taels.
Ten years,
5,000 taels.
I don't think the number is right.
How is it wrong?
For ten years,
has he been an official with integrity
or has he hidden himself too well?
Perhaps he was working with someone else
to transport the stolen money.
The last 5,000 taels left
was only the leftover amount.
Where's the other stolen money?
The Ministry of Justice didn't investigate
and it wasn't included in the dossier.
Perhaps he used the money
to purchase soldiers and horses.
Then he should be suspected of treason.
The Court of Judicial Review's minister
wants to kill him without investigation.
If you think carefully,
aren't you worried?
We must investigate it in detail.
However, we have no new evidence
to reopen this case.
What should we do?
That is why
I brought the people of Huaixiang
to the capital.
I'd like to summon witnesses.
Approved.
Summon the witnesses.
Kneel!
Regarding Magistrate Xue Huaiyuan's
corruption case,
what do you have to say?
Your Majesty,
I don't know
about Magistrate Xue's corruption case.
I only know…
Raise your head and speak.
I only know that both my daughter
and I would be bullied
and have nowhere to live
if it wasn't for Magistrate Xue.
After my husband died,
- I raised my child alone.
- Mother.
- At our most difficult time,
- Don't be afraid.
Magistrate Xue
used his own salary to subsidize us.
He Jun,
help them clean up.
If someone dares bully them,
punish them according to the law.
- Yes.
- Ping'an.
Go and thank Magistrate Xue. Hurry.
- Thank you, Mr. Xue.
- All right.
It's fine now.
No one would dare to bully you again.
If Magistrate Xue hadn't sponsored me,
I might still be illiterate.
My family was poor
and I couldn't afford tuition.
Magistrate Xue generously
gave me travel expenses
so I could return to the academy
and become a scholar.
Gu Da.
Give him money to study.
Get the money from my salary.
- Yes.
- Mother.
- My son.
- I can study again.
Yes. That's great.
They said the pork I sold
would cause death.
If it wasn't for Magistrate Xue,
my ancestors' assets
would've been taken by the bullies.
Stop!
I wanted to pay Magistrate Xue,
but he refused.
Your Majesty,
please investigate.
Magistrate Xue
will never commit corruption.
Magistrate Xue is a good person.
- Yes.
- Magistrate Xue is a good person.
- He's a good man.
- He wouldn't do that.
Yes!
That's what they say.
Paying them
to speak for the corrupt official
isn't that hard either.
Duke Zhou,
you need to be careful.
The Vice Minister of Justice is right.
Why would a corrupt official
do so much for the people?
I'm sure these people were bribed
and spoke nonsense.
Please summon other witnesses.
Summon the witnesses.
Kneel!
Magistrate Xue paved
my home entrance's road.
There was a flood
and Magistrate Xue
did not return home for three days.
Magistrate Xue gave me money
to treat my illness.
Magistrate's Xue's grace…
- Magistrate Xue's kindness…
- If it wasn't for Magistrate Xue…
Your Majesty, please investigate clearly!
- Your Majesty, please investigate clearly!
What they said sounds touching.
They remind me
of the corruption case three years ago
by the magistrate of Qingzhou.
The magistrate embezzled
a huge amount of money back then
but used a small amount
to help the people.
When we seized his assets,
there were also many people
who knelt and pleaded
for him like them.
You personally handled the case,
Minister Zhou.
Have you forgotten?
I still remember it well.
Chancellor Li, you are right.
Spending a small amount on the people
and a big amount on buying lands, right?
The Great Yan does have
such a greedy official.
Feng Yutang is one of them.
Half a year after Feng Yutang
became the magistrate of Huaixiang,
he bought furniture for himself.
His family wore a lot of jewelry
and they lived a lavish lifestyle.
Xue Huaiyuan worked there for ten years.
I'm sure he had more assets than him.
Half a year ago,
Xue Huaiyuan was imprisoned
and his assets were seized.
I request the Grand Censor
to announce the assets seized
from the Xue family
and the Feng family.
Show everyone
how much worse
Xue Huaiyuan is compared to Feng Yutang.
Grand Censor, please present
the two magistrates' assets.
The former magistrate of Huaixiang,
Xue Huaiyuan,
had no houses or lands
when he was in office.
The amount of stolen money
seized from his residence
and his total assets
amount to a total of 5,000 taels.
- That…
- That's not right.
The current magistrate of Huaixiang,
Feng Yutang,
has more than 40 houses
while he is in office.
The farmland he owns is too much to count.
After investigation,
his houses, farmlands, and savings
exceeded a total of 200,000 tales.
What? Over 200,000 taels?
He has more than 200,000 taels?
A complicated 200,000 taels
and a clean 5,000 taels.
In that case,
Magistrate Xue didn't even leave himself
a piece of roof tile in Huaixiang.
He only embezzled 5,000 taels.
And the money
was all exchanged into ingots
and put into crates
in his own residence, waiting
for the Ministry of Justice's seizure.
He is indeed an example
for corrupt officials.
Stop using your eloquent words.
No matter how much
and how he got the money,
he is still corrupt.
Minister Zhou,
please summon other witnesses.
Summon the witnesses.
Your Majesty,
we were officers of Huaixiang
when Magistrate Xue was in office.
Magistrate Xue stayed in Huaixiang
for ten years.
He was never corrupt.
After he was imprisoned,
all of us who knew the truth
were confined in a mine.
Your Majesty!
We are willing to swear on our lives.
If we tell a lie, punish us
by nine familial exterminations.
We are willing to swear on our lives.
If we tell a lie, punish us
by nine familial exterminations!
We are willing to swear on our lives.
If we tell a lie, punish us
by nine familial exterminations.
We are willing to swear on our lives.
If we tell a lie, punish us
by nine familial exterminations!
- We are willing to swear on our lives.
- If we tell a lie, punish us
- by nine familial exterminations.
No matter what,
it is true that Xue Huaiyuan was corrupt.
As Ms. Jiang Li mentioned,
he should be punished
with death by a thousand slashes.
Hold it.
Jiang Li,
go on.
The magistrate of Huaixiang,
Xue Huaiyuan, committed a crime.
His crime is that in the ten years
he was in the position,
apart from embezzling
the disaster relief funds,
he had almost no desires
and was loyal,
responsible,
and upright.
It's hard to find
a corrupt official like him.
So during his term,
he must have had many schemes
and evil actions.
During his term,
where did his money go?
Building dams and footpaths
and benefiting the people.
He was trying to embarrass
the good officials in the capital
who live a lavish life
and own hectares of land.
He was shameless and arrogant!
Xue Huaiyuan's crime
is unforgivable indeed.
I request Your Majesty
to punish Xue Huaiyuan
with death by a thousand slashes.
In that case,
Xue Huaiyuan did not commit a crime
but had merits instead.
I request
that Xue Huaiyuan be brought to the hall.
Xue Huaiyuan is a witness as well.
I want Your Majesty
to see what Magistrate Xue looks like now.
Approved.
Summon Xue Huaiyuan.
Your Majesty,
this man is Xue Huaiyuan,
the magistrate of Huaixiang.
He was imprisoned by Feng Yutang
and was heavily tortured.
He is now mentally confused
and behaves like a child.
What a pity that an upright official
ended up like this.
If news of this spreads,
how many upright officials
in the nation will feel disappointed?
And how many people
will swear loyalty to Your Majesty?
How dare you, Jiang Li!
How dare you doubt His Majesty?
Ms. Jiang Li's sentiment
is coincidentally similar to mine.
Sincere advice
may be unpleasant to the ear.
Ms. Jiang Li's words might be out of line,
but they sound reasonable.
If we abandon upright officials
and only use corrupt officials,
the nation will be in ruins.
Duke Su is right.
I'm not someone
who can't take sincere advice.
Minister Jiang,
you raised your daughter well.
Such an upright official
who loves the people
was falsely accused and sent to prison.
Now, he is in such a pitiful state.
This is my fault
and a loss for Great Yan!
- We are to blame.
Rise.
Wei Qian!
You misjudged a case.
Do you admit your guilt?
I deserve to die!
I didn't know
there was such a nefarious person
in my administration
like Feng Yutang.
Zhou Dezhao, I order you to reinvestigate
Xue Huaiyuan's corruption case.
Those who were involved
in framing Xue Huaiyuan
should be punished severely!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Jiang Li,
you are brave and wise.
You impressed me once again.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You may rise.
Xue Huaiyuan's case
has been investigated clearly.
Mr. Zhou, you should judge
Ms. Jiang Li's case
of breaking a prisoner out of jail.
Your Majesty.
My daughter is reckless indeed.
But after hearing the truth
about Xue Huaiyuan's case earlier,
I'm really reluctant to punish her
for what she did that day.
A good official's unjust death
is not just a tragedy to himself
but a hit to every official's loyalty.
My daughter made a grave mistake,
but she saved a good official
whom I couldn't save.
In this main hall today,
I…
I feel ashamed.
We are ashamed!
- We are ashamed!
Zhou Dezhao,
what do you say?
Your Majesty,
since Xue Huaiyuan was wronged,
that means he is not a criminal.
So there's no evidence that Ms. Jiang Li
broke a prisoner out of jail.
That is reasonable.
Jiang Li,
you are acquitted.
You may close your case at
the Court of Judicial Review and go home.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Rise.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Does Xue Huaiyuan have children
and family members?
I want to compensate them.
Xue Huaiyuan had a son and a daughter.
As far as I know,
his son, Xue Zhao,
was killed by bandits
in the capital last year.
His daughter, Xue Fangfei…
was Mr. Shen's late wife.
This is too pitiful.
- Right.
- Yes.
- So heartbreaking.
- That's right.
When I found out my father-in-law
had committed corruption,
I was shocked.
Now that I've learned
that he was framed by a villain,
it pains me
now that I recall it.
Father.
It was tough for you.
Ye Shijie.
Magistrate Xue,
it's all right.
It's fine now.
Magistrate Xue, it's all right.
Mr. Shen, please forgive him.
You haven't seen Magistrate Xue
for a long time.
I'm afraid he can't recognize you anymore.
Duke Zhou, Magistrate Xue is in shock.
Can I take him back to rest first?
You may leave.
Who wrote this story?
It's really cruel.
What do you mean?
The father is corrupt.
The daughter had an affair.
The son was murdered.
The family of three suffered tragic fates
one after the other.
Isn't this common in storybooks?
What storybook?
Framing
and silencing people.
Framing?
Was Mr. Shen's late wife framed
for having an affair as well?
We can't be sure.
Duke Su has always been bold.
- He dares to say anything.
- Yes.
Duke Su, I'll leave this matter to you.
Investigate the truth
behind the deaths of the Xues
and clear the family's name
so Mr. Shen can feel relieved.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Interesting.
How interesting.
Why didn't Your Majesty ask me to join
such an interesting imperial court trial?
An investigation is not child's play.
Why did you come here?
I have something important
to inform you about.
Ms. Jiang Li has a sharp tongue.
She has successfully overturned
the Xue family's case.
While Your Majesty feels indignant
about your upright subject being framed,
I wonder if you have thought
you were also being played
like a fool?
Wanning,
don't speak nonsense.
What a coincidence.
I heard Mr. Shen's wife
was Huaixiang's most talented lady,
so I got curious and went to take a look.
Indeed.
Mrs. Shen has a unique face.
It was rare indeed.
That's why I was shocked
when I saw Ms. Jiang Li.
Because she looks exactly the same
as Xue Fangfei.
- What?
- Is that so?